Nicholas Matos

630-203-7072 mnick708@gmail.com 819 North College Avenue Unit I-122, Tempe, Arizona

Summary

Energetic, enthusiastic, determined, a self-motivated individual with experience in IT HelpDesk, Network Support, Hardware Troubleshooting, and CRM Software. Research, Education, and Customer Experience are first and foremost.

Skills

Help Desk, Technology, Network Support, Customer Service Skills, Management Experience, Operating Systems

Experience

The Maynard Group, Inc.

IT Support/ Helpdesk, Tempe, Arizona

01/2022 - 12/2022

Maintain quality customer service while troubleshooting and asking targeted clarifying questions to clearly understand any issue I can not resolve myself.

Research and implement solutions for any issue that falls within my scope, partner with leadership in order to find the proper solution for each client.

Maintain information integrity in all servers and storage locations for client information, ensure that records are accurately maintained.

Remain up to date on all systems company uses for communications and information tracking. Train/ self educate in any area I believe myself to be weak in.

Guaranteed Rate Inc.

Closing Coordinator, Chicago, Illinois 08/2020 - 11/2021

Maintain pipeline and coordinate with team to meet all necessary deadlines in a fast-paced environment. Communicate with borrowers, title companies, and third parties to accommodate timely closing. Maintain working knowledge of all computer systems and updates as they roll out.

Track and organize all closing documents before sending to final review team before signing.

Wis international

Apple Brand Technician, Phoenix, Arizona

08/2018 - 07/2020

Work in conjunction with Apple to roll out new display devices as well as their supporting software during product launches.

Maintain display devices as well as the smart displays they connect to, troubleshoot and repair any and all issues. Update software and repair hardware as needed for displays and devices.

Retain working knowledge of all current Apple devices to aid vendors in troubleshooting.

Manage scheduling for vendor routes and travel out of state.

Marketsource

EEL/ Store Manager, Rosemont, Illinois

01/2015 - 08/2018

Ensured my team always exceeded sales goals without fail.

Created and managed multiple district wide training campaigns as well as the training of my own team. Developed multiple apps (IOS, Android) for training and job aides for my district leadership and team members.

Maintained advanced knowledge of all technology carried in store locations.

Managerial tasks - hiring, scheduling, disciplinary meetings, leadership conferences.

Education

Web Development Bootcamp

University of Arizona, Gilbert, Arizona HTML, JavaScript, CSS, Bootstrap, React

High School Diploma

Lyons Township High School, LaGrange, IL 06/2014

Languages

English

Certificates

A+ Certificate (Expired - able to renew), Net+ Certificate (Expired - able to renew)